Nevada Folklife Archive
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 1: Audiocassettes
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Side A: Performance of African American Dance by Children of the Diaspora African Musical Ensemble (CODAME), Side B: Performance of Mexican dance by Ballet Folklorico St. John's from Moapa, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-019; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Side A: Performance by Warburton Family Bluegrass Band, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-020; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival: Side A and B: Performances of cowboy poetry by Mike Prince, and Jewish stories by Hester Katzman, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-021; 1 sound cassette
    - Sierra Highlanders, June 20, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-022; 1 sound cassette
    - Randy Stowell (master) rawhide braiding, Hank Brackenbury (apprentice), March 9, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-001 - C-1996-003; Andrea Graham; 3 sound cassettes
    - Interview with John Massie and Weston Hallam about the Scottish bag piping apprenticeship, October 7, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-004 - C-1996-005; Andrea Graham and Nicholas Curchin Vrooman; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with the Fort Mojave Elders of Needles, California, June 24, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-006; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Richard Arnold, Pahrump Paiute Director, Las Vegas Indian Center, July 9, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-007; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Lolavi Miller, Moapa Cultural Resources Tribal Office, July 11, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-008; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Christine Stones, Vice Chair, Ely Shoshone Colony, July 12, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-009; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Keith Honacker, Shoshone Tribal Chair, July 15, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-010; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Duckwater Women Elders: Sofia Allison, Pauline Blackeye, Helen Walker, Noreen George, Irene Mike, July 15, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-011; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - James Birchim, Yomba Tribal Chairman, July 16, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-012; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Stillwater elders: Floyd Hatch, Ione Howard, Bea Roman, Marie Ellison, July 19, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-013; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Interview with Antoinette Cavanaugh, Vice Principal, Spring Creek High School - Duck Valley Shoshone, August 13, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-014-; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Interview at Wells Shoshone Colony Council Meeting. Andrea Woods is Chair. Also present are Harvey Healy, Gracie Begay, Susanna Panoly, Charlotte Healy, August 13, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-015; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Interview with several members of the Battle Mountain Band of Shoshone. Vicki Yorenda, Claudette "Dee" Reynolds, Verdine Ravis, Clarence Ambrosy. Claudette "Dee" Reynolds is the tribal administrator, August 14, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-016; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Interview with Corbin Harney and Nina Aponte at the colony offices in Battle Mountain, August 30, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-017 - C-1996-018; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Interview with Harold Miller, tribal chair of the Walker River Paiutes, and Lou Lockwood, Council Member, recorded at the Walker River Reservation in Schurz, September 6, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-019; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Fourth Annual Las Vegas Folklife Festival: Side A: Red Tail Singers, April 27, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-020; 1 sound cassette
    - Fourth Annual Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Lorenzi Park's Sammy Davis, Jr. Festival Plaza: Side A: Kaminari Taiko Drummers, Side B: Las Vegas Hawaiian Civic Club's Gracious Ladies, April 27, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-021; 1 sound cassette
    - Fourth Annual Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Lorenzi Park's Sammy Davis, Jr. Festival Plaza: Side A: Visions of Praise, Side B: Hi Steppers Drill Team, April 27, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-022; 1 sound cassette
    - Fourth Annual Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Lorenzi Park's Sammy Davis, Jr. Festival Plaza, Side A: Seamus and Seamus (Irish American), Side B: Mike Prince, Corey Haydn, April 27, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-023; 1 sound cassette
    - Fourth Annual Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Lorenzi Park's Sammy Davis, Jr. Festival Plaza, Side A: Marty Warburton Band, Side B: Las Vegas Highland Pipe and Drums, April 27, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-024; 1 sound cassette
    - Rebecca Rushing interviews Sarrama and John George in Las Vegas, September 18, 1996, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-025; Rebecca Rushing; 1 sound cassette
    - Alfreda L. Mitra, Las Vegas Paiute Colony Tribal Chair, July 9, 1996, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1996-027; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Interview with John Massie and Weston Hallam about the Scottish bag piping apprenticeship, March 10, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-001; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviewed Ida Mae Valdez (master), Lillius Richardson, Marlin Thompson (apprentice), Clara Rogers Howell. Paiute apprenticeship in medicinal plants, February 10, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-002 - C-1997-003; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Darlene Dewey (master) and Melanie Bryan (apprentice) on Shoshone basketry apprenticeship, March 7, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-004 - C-1997-005; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview Francine Tohannie (master) and Harriet Allen (apprentice) on Shoshone-Paiute dressmaking apprenticeship, March 8, 1997, Andrea Graham
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-006 - C-1997-007; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Interview with Elizabeth Brady (master) and Lois Whitney (apprentice), apprenticeship in Shoshone songs. Recorded at Elizabeth's house. Elizabeth is Lois' mother, April 11, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-008 - C-1997-009; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Lois Whitney sings (taught by Elizabeth Brady) in Shoshone, translates into English, explains meaning. Lois made tape, sent with written report. 000-173 Minnows; 037-051 Dance of the Sage Hen; 077-089 Spring Showers; 100-116 Snow Mountain; 130-150 Nite Song, April 11, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-010; Lois Whitney; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviewed Jean McNicoll (master), and Jeanne O'Daye (apprentice) about the apprenticeship in Washoe basketry, at Carson Colony Gym. Jeanne is Jean's niece, April 21, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-011; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviewed Norma Smokey (master), and her daughter Colleen Hernandez (apprentice) about the apprenticeship in Washoe basketry, at their home, April 21, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-012; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviewed Ivie Garfield (master), and Sharon Barton (apprentice) about the apprenticeship in Paiute basketry and cradleboards, at Ivie's house, April 24, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-013; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviewed Leah Brady (master), Marian Sam and Arvilla Johnny (apprentices) about the apprenticeship in Shoshone basketry, at Elizabeth Brady's house in Elko. (Elizabeth is Leah's mother, and she is also present), December 15, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-014 - C-1997-015; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - John Massie sample tunes taught to Wes during the past eight months. Played by pipe major John Massie (master) and Wes Hallam (apprentice), 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-016; 1 sound cassette
    - Tape provided by John Massie. Side 1 is solo selections (performed in Santa Monica); Side 2 is selections by the Los Angeles Police Pipe Band, pipe major and soloist John Massie, 1997, AFC 2017/002: C-1997-017; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with John Massie and Wes Hallam, in the second year of their apprenticeships. Scottish bag piping. Hornpipe, February 17, 1998, AFC 2017/002: C-1998-001 - C-1998-002; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Barbara Lierly, Polish paper cutting apprenticeship (master was Frances Drwal of Illinois. Nevada Arts Council folklorist Eliza Buck is also present), February 18, 1998, AFC 2017/002: C-1998-003; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Apprenticeship in Paiute singing. Master Wesley Jim, apprentice Marlin Thompson discussing their apprenticeship at the senior center at the Walker River Paiute Reservation, March 20, 1998, AFC 2017/002: C-1998-004; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Apprenticeship in Filipino Rondalla music. Master Lyn Perry and apprentices Gloria Fosgate and Katrina Opena at Lyn's classroom at Lake Elementary School, April 1, 1998, AFC 2017/002: C-1998-005; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Apprenticeship in Shoshone-Paiute round willow baskets. Interview with master Bernardine DeLorme and apprentice Linda Comas working in the backyard of Bernie's house in Reno, August 8, 1998, AFC 2017/002: C-1998-006 - C-1998-007; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Apprenticeship in star quilting, interview with master Edna Mae Johnson and apprentice Karen Wahwasuck at Edna's house on the Reno-Sparks Indian Colony, September 2, 1998, Andrea Graham
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-1998-008; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Community Roots discussion, three tapes, labeled "AAW" (African American women?), recorded in Las Vegas, October 17, 1998, AFC 2017/002: C-1998-009; Andrea Graham; 3 sound cassettes
    - Paiute storytelling; Andrew Allen, master and Marlin Thompson, apprentice, March 18, 1999, AFC 2017/002: C-1999-001; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Tape of Paiute stories in English, told by Andrew Allen; tape made by Andrew Allen, March 18, 1999, AFC 2017/002: C-1999-002 - C-1999-003; Andrew Allen; 2 sound cassettes
    - Paiute willow basketry; master Charlotte Dunnett, apprentice Charissa Dunnett (Charlotte's daughter), October 6, 1999, AFC 2017/002: C-1999-004; Nicholas Curchin Vrooman; 1 sound cassette
    - Folk Arts Apprenticeship FY00 - Rawhide braiding; master Doug Groves, apprentice Grant Groves (Doug's son). Ranch is near Battle Mountain, twelve miles north of Dry Creek, January 24, 2000, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-001 - C-2000-002; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Folk Arts Apprenticeship FY00 - Paiute leather work; master Raphael Bell, apprentice Raymond Montoya, February 29, 2000, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-003 - C-2000-004; Nicholas Curchin Vrooman; 2 sound cassettes
    - Folk Arts Apprenticeship FY00 - Polish paper cutting (wycinanki); master Barbara Glinski, apprentice Magdalena Glinski (Barbara's daughter), April 6, 2000, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-005; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Folk Arts Apprenticeship FY00 - Scottish bag piping; master John Massie (Hollywood, California), apprentice Josh Underwood (Las Vegas), April 7, 2000, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-006; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Folk Arts Apprenticeship FY00 - Ukrainian Easter eggs (pysanky); master Zoria Zetaruk, apprentice Nicholas Yakowenko, April 7, 2000, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-007; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Folk Arts Apprenticeship FY00 - Shoshone-Paiute round dance songs; master Art Cavanaugh (deceased), apprentice Grayson Huitt, April 30, 2000, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-008; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Folk Arts Apprenticeship FY00 - Paiute buckskin tanning; master Myra Whitney, apprentice Charles Robert "Bobby" Wadsworth, May 10, 2000, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-009; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with [Andy Mazzotti] cigar maker, April 12, 2000, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2000-010; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Site visit with folklife master artist Joey Lavadour and apprentice Kathleen Thompson at Joey's home in Reno, showing Pendleton-style (Oregon) baskets, September 29, 2001, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2001-001; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Sunny Martin], March 4, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-001; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Pete Paris], March 8, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-002; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Bessie Kulias], April 2, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-003; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Dave Moore], April 3, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-004 - C-2002-005; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Jay Godfrey], April 4, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-006; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Patsy Schlabsz], May 9, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-007 - C-2002-008; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Dean Baker], May 9, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-009; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Terry Ishii Hase], May 10, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-010; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Elizabeth Brady and Leah Brady], July 13, 2002, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-011; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Laura Fillmore], October 18, 2002, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-012-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Steve Furimsky and Zoria Zetaruk], April 24, 2002, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-013; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Keith Hodges (D-Bar Hats)], October 14, 2002, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-014; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Andrew Lum and Billie Ann Sabala], October 14, 2002, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-015-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Al Tietjen], February 7, 2002, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-016-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Yoko Arana and Mimi Thompson], July 30, 2002, Christina Barr and Irma Varela Wynants
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-025-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Carrie Black], August 6, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-026-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Israel Favela], August 12, 2002, Christina Barr and Irma Varela Wynants
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-027-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Shadow Mountain Quilters group], August 15, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-028-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Barbara Griffith], August 15, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-029-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Victoria Brazzle], August 15, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-030; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Wilma Myers], August 26, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-031-AC; 3 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Susie Finlay], August 27, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-032-AC; 3 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Girtia Lukes], September 10, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-033-AC; 3 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Dawna Joliff], September 11, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-034-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Jody Cotton], September 11, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-035-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Jill Halverson and Linda Heckendorf], September 26, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-036-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Marjorie Stanbridge], October 1, 2002, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-037-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Mary Sharp], October 16, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-038-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Frieda Bronfin], October 16, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-039-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Janett Rice], October 17, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-040-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Elena Nunta], December 18, 2002, AFC 2017/002: C-2002-041-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Elaine Smokey], September 25, 2003, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-001; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Cynthia Kannan and Sue Coleman], January 30, 2003, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-002; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Mohammed Darehbaghi], May 3, 2003, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-003; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Ralph Charlie and Marlin Thompson], March 4, 2003, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-004; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Zeny Ocean], April 19, 2003, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-005-AC; 3 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Horst Essl], August 4, 2003, Penny Rucks
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-007; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Andy Allen], April 2, 2003, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-008; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Doug Groves], March 10, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-009-AB; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Michelle Gibbons], May 7, 2003, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-010; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Virgene Hardy], March 12, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-011; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Zoria Zetaruk], January 13, 2003, Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-025-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Nancy Williams Baker], February 25, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-026-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Quilts 4 Cancer group], June 11, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-027-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Barb Johnston and Ginny Waite], June 11, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-028-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Barbara Cleveland], June 19, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-029; Christina Barr; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Pahrump Shadow Mountain Quilters group], June 19, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-030-AB; Christina Barr; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Elena Nunta], June 30, 2003, AFC 2017/002: C-2003-031-AB; Christina Barr and Irma Varela Wynants; 2 sound cassettes
    - [Interview with Iola Byers], April 17, 2004, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-001; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Elena Nunta, Vilma Parra, and Maria Sanchez], June 14, 2004, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-002; Anne F. Hatch and Irma Varela Wynants; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Maggi Davis], July 5, 2004, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-003; Penny Rucks; 1 sound cassette
    - [Interview with Edward McDade], July 6, 2004, Anne F. Hatch and Christina Barr
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-004-AB; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Elaine Smokey], August 20, 2004, Anne F. Hatch
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-005; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Everett Pikyavit], July 28, 2004, Anne F. Hatch and Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-006 - C-2004-007; 2 sound cassettes
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 2 text files (.doc)
    - [Interview with Girtia Lukes], June 15, 2004, Anne F. Hatch
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-008; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with JoAnn Martinez], July 7, 2004, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-009; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Mateo Masellones], August 4, 2004, Penny Rucks
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-010; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Rosemary Rogers de Soto], November 18, 2004, Jeanne Harrah Johnson
      - Sound recording, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-011; 1 sound cassette
      - Interview transcript, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.doc)
    - [Interview with Virginia McCuin], August 18, 2004, Anne F. Hatch
      - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/002: C-2004-012-AB; 2 sound cassettes